Chris Jacobs

1337 Steele St. Denver, Co 80206 | (303) 842-5484 | LinkedIn: /chris-jacobs-design | Portfolio: https://cjacobs20.github.io/design_develope_portfolio/christianejacobs2020@gmail.com

UX/UI Designer with biology undergraduate degree and background in fine art and digital art. Graduate of University of Denver and Metropolitan University of Denver with department diverse hospital experience, in combination with the ability to utilize various design methods and applications including Figma and Adobe XD, wireframing and prototyping, product research, user research, usability testing and competitive analysis to create, redesign and iterate multi-platform applications in order to curate the best user experience a product can offer.

SKILLS

Tools: Epic Beaker, Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop, Adobe Premier, Miro, InVision

Research: User Interviews, Multi-platform Surveys

Generative: Storyboarding, Prototyping, Affinity Mapping, Journey Mapping,

Wireframing, User Persona Curating

Summative: Heuristic Evaluation, Usability Testing

Programming: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap

PROJECTS

Community Basket App Design |

A team project of creating a mobile application encouraging household waste reduction/repurposing and donation; Community Basket. This project involved organic group effort throughout, dissected into calculated group concordance during initial research and empathy phases, then onto more specialized roles during prototyping and development.

Homegrown Application Design | Homegrown Case Study

A team oriented project with the goal of producing and designing a mobile application to help our users to be successful in all things plant ownership related. In our team of three, roles of UX/UI design, deliverable production and proposal were split evenly with a proposal deadline of three weeks.

Denver Art Society Redesign |

A solo project aimed at revitalizing the website for the Denver Art Society. Three weeks start-to-finish profited an entirely new design and user flow for the organization, centralized around showcasing resident artists and giving users ample reason and affordance to donate to the organization.

EXPERIENCE

February 2019-Present HISTOLOGY TECHNICIAN, ST. ANTHONY'S HISTOLOGY LABORATORY

Patient case management; tissue processing, staining qualitative and quantitative inspection and reporting. Quality control of stained slides and sign off before pathologic review. Shift-to-shift communications and task delegation and general management. Machine troubleshooting, work around and site-to-site communications on such.

January 2019-February 2019 HISTOLOGY EXTERN, ST. ANTHONY'S HISTOLOGY LABORATORY

Tissue embedding, microtomy and staining including standard H&E, Immunohistochemistry, and special staining. Slide triage and turnout after quality control inspection. Laboratory machine maintenance, including solution production and quality control.

October 2018-January 2019 HISTOLOGY ASSISTANT, ST. ANTHONY'S HISTOLOGY LABORATORY

Tissue accessioning, processing and disposal. Tissue processing appliance maintenance specialist, utilization and upkeep of machine processes and reagent reservoirs. Act as liaison between mortuary and hospital to ensure appropriate burial of products of conception. Assist histology technicians to manage slides, including but not limited to; staining, triaging, dispersal and allocation.

June 2014-December 2018 SHIFT MANAGER, COLORADO CIDER CO.

Customer service representative. Tasting room and event specialist. Cellar hand. Promoted to shift manager with responsibilities including, but not limited to; drafting and implementing staff scheduling, and weekend on-call problem solving.

EDUCATION

January 2022 UNIVERSITY OF DENVER, UX/UI Certificate
June 2019 AMERICAN SOCIETY FOR CLINICAL PATHOLOGY, Histotechnologist license (HTL)

June 2019 AMERICAN SOCIETY FOR CLINICAL PATHOLOGY, Digital Pathology Certificate July 2018 METROPOLITAN UNIVERSITY OF DENVER, DENVER, CO, Bachelor of Arts Undergraduate Major: B.A. Biology, w/ Ecology focus | Undergraduate Minor: Studio Art